[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'хоббі' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅみ"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'готівка' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "げんきん"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'щоденник' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "にっき"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'збирати, колекціонувати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あつめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'грати (на струнних та клавішних інструментах)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'прати, мити' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あらいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'співати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うたいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'обмінювати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'водити (машину)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うんてんします"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Передбачити, прогнозувати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "よそくします"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відвідувати, оглядати, йти на екскурсію,практику' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんがくします"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the word 'Это опасно, моторошно, блин' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ヤバイ"
    }
]